(Raj:)Interesting. Did they take a walk
down Liars'Lane?
(Leonard:)- What?
- A lane frequented by liars.
(Raj:)Like you, you big liar.
- You have her?
- Thank God she's okay.
(Raj:)Well, I trusted you and you let me down.
The poor thing's been shaking for hours.
- I'm really sorry.
- Hang on, you've had her for hours?
(Raj:)Yes. I picked her up and then we both went
for massages to try and calm down.
(Raj:)And then we got Pinkberry.
(Bernadette:)You knew she was okay and you couldn't
pick up the phone to tell us?
- Well, I thought about...
- Don't "well" me, mister.
(Bernadette:)We've been worried sick.
(Bernadette:)She could have been dead for all we knew.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
- Sorry, I just...
- Sorry's not good enough.
(Bernadette:)Maybe you need to take some time
and think about what you've done.
Nice guilt trip. Heh.
You are gonna be an amazing mom.